<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What is Open Cluster Management? on Open Cluster Management</title>
    <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What is Open Cluster Management? on Open Cluster Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://open-cluster-management.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/concepts/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/concepts/architecture/</guid>
      <description>This page tells you the architecture and basic concepts in open-cluster-management.
   Hub cluster Klusterlet Managed cluster Application lifecycle  Application console (work in progress)   Cluster lifecycle (work in progress)  Discovery (work in progress)   Governance and risk (work in progress) Multiclusterhub Operator (work in progress)  Multiclusterhub Repo (work in progress)   Search (work in progress) Observing environments     Hub cluster The hub cluster is the common term that is used to define the central controller that runs in a Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute to Open Cluster Management</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/contribute/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/contribute/contribute/</guid>
      <description>We know you&amp;rsquo;ve got great ideas for improving Open Cluster Management. So roll up your sleeves and come join us in the community!
Getting Started All contributions are welcome! Open Cluster Management uses the Apache 2 license. Please open issues for any bugs or problems you encounter, ask questions in the #open-cluster-mgmt on Kubernetes Slack Channel, or get involved joining the open-cluster-management mailing group.
Contribute to the Source  Join the Mailing group Attend an upcoming Community meetings Fork the repository you wish to work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/community/resource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/community/resource/</guid>
      <description>Join conversations with the other people who are involved in the creation, maintenance, and future of open-cluster-management. We want to hear from you. How you are using open-cluster-management? What we can do to make it better? To understand how the Open Cluster Management community is governed, visit the Community repo.
Get Connected See the following options to connect with the community:
GitHub
Mailing group
Slack
Community meetings
YouTube channel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/concepts/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/concepts/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>This page tells you the roadmap for components in open-cluster-management.
Work in progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Cluster Manager</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-cluster-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-cluster-manager/</guid>
      <description>The are two ways to install the core control plane of open cluster management that includes cluster registration and manifests distribution.
   Prerequisite Install from source Install from OperatorHub     Prerequisite Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
Ensure golang is installed, if you are planning to install from the source.
Prepare one Kubernetes cluster to function as the hub. For example, use kind to create a hub cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Klusterlet</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/register-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/register-cluster/</guid>
      <description>After the cluster manager is installed on the hub cluster, you need to install the klusterlet agent on another cluster so that it can be registered and managed by the hub cluster.
   Prerequisite Install from source Install from OperatorHub What is next     Prerequisite Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
Ensure golang is installed, if you are planning to install from the source.
Ensure the open-cluster-management cluster manager is installed on the hub cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Application management</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-application/</guid>
      <description>After the cluster manager is installed, you could install the application management components to the hub cluster.
   Prerequisite Install from source Install from OperatorHub What is next     Prerequisite Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
Ensure golang is installed, if you are planning to install from the source.
Ensure the open-cluster-management cluster manager is installed. See Install Cluster Manager for more information.
Install from source Clone the multicloud-operators-subscription</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Discovery</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-discovery/</guid>
      <description>After the hub is installed, the discovery component can be installed to help discover available clusters.
   Install from source     Install from source To build, run, and sample the discovery operator, clone the repository below and follow the instructions within the README.
git clone https://github.com/open-cluster-management/discovery.git </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install MultiClusterHub Operator</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-multiclusterhub-operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-multiclusterhub-operator/</guid>
      <description>Install from source To build and install the MultiClusterHub Operator as a standalone component, follow the CONTRIBUTING guide referenced in the source README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Policy Framework</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-policy-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-policy-framework/</guid>
      <description>After the cluster manager and klusterlet are installed, you can install the policy framework components to the hub and the managed clusters.
   Prerequisite Install from prebuilt images on Quay.io     Prerequisite You must meet the following prerequisites to install the policy framework:
  Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
  Ensure Golang is installed, if you are planning to install from the source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Policy Controllers</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-policy-controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.github.io/getting-started/install-policy-controllers/</guid>
      <description>After policy framework is installed, you can install the policy controllers to the managed clusters.
   Prerequisite Install the configuration policy controller Install the certificate policy controller Install the IAM policy controller What is next More policies     Prerequisite You must meet the following prerequisites to install the policy controllers:
  Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
  Ensure Golang is installed, if you are planning to install from the source.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>